Hi, my name's Cindy Mastry with Yoga Etc.
This is April and April is going to help demonstrate in this clip the Compass pose.
April is seated in Dandasana lengthening up from the tailbone to her crown and reaching out through her heels.
She's going to bring the soles of her feet together and allow her knees to fall out to the sides coming into Baddha Konasana or bound angle.
She's then going to take her right foot and bring it up and take her right hand underneath her knee and take her right hand back to the ground by her hip.
She's going to lengthen up she'd going to reach her hand toward her foot and try to lengthen it up over her head.
She's stretching through this side massaging the muscles on the other side.
She's then going to release the foot and take her arm around for a bind and then she's going to point the toe toward the Compass point.
Coming into the twist and bind - that's beautiful.
And then she's going to very slowly come out of it.
It's important to come out of a pose slowly.
And then extending the legs back into her Dandasana and that's the Compass pose.